[{"answer": "Look, I know you had some problems with your father, and he and my frien", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "--but my friend was my salvation", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Something wrong", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Got him here", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "That the word on our boy", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Skinny", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Name's my friend", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend what", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "One of my friend's boys", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "As I remember it was because he had a sassy mouth on him. Must run in the famil", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Runnin' numbers without I know about it is both illegal and unhealthy. You remember that", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How come you don't took familiar", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "that place, huh? I hear they let you boys run wild up there", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Mami, how old were you when my fathe", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Right. When he was killed", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "There must have been somebody", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Nobody's too busy", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Es muy lindo, su coch", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Is very beautiful, your car", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend look at thi", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It's a .45", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It can happen so sudden, can't it? Being left out on your own", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "They've got me. Different thing", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "White man just using you to keep the Black man down", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You suckers haven't had a good day since the that place", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " The Republicans", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "They got telephones", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "N", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Gotta be in person", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "And what did she do", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "that place school, nasty", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Sure, they go back to that place. When he rode by, they were squatting in a hut cooking hamsters for dinner", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "All my mother does is work. That's how you get to be Spanish", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "All my mother does is work. That's how you get to be Spanish", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "The Sheriff", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Same as they done in that place", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "They were in the that place. Like your father", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " You know who I am", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That guy who got sho", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Didn't have a father", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "When you're his age you'll still be pissed off about him", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "my friend went on like you were that guy who won the Gulf War. Colin whatsit", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "He never asked her", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "In English, my friend. We're in the that plac", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You have somebody else out there", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I am marry to the cousin of a frien", "docId": "Lone-Star.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "We have a daughter", "qsentId": 48}]